

GAME DESIGNER

### **Details**

Av. Villazon Km 4 1/2, Cochabamba, Bolivia kevin031995@gmail.com +591 72\*\*\*\*(Request by E-Mail)

#### Links

LinkedIn

Portfolio

Itch.io Page

## **Latest Game Projects**

Sacred Tails (PC-Win)
Long Delivery (PC-Win)

#### Skills

Game Development

Game Design

2D animation

Unity 3D

Communication

Ability to Work in a Team

**Manual Testing** 

**Automated Web Testing** 

## Languages

English

Spanish

## Favorite Action Multiplayer Games

Dark souls, Bloodborne, Risk of Rain 2, Genshin Impact.

### **Profile**

Professional game developer with more than 6 years developing games. And quality assurance engineer with 3 years of work experience.

As a game developer, I have worked on commercial and hobbyist projects for mobile and PC platforms, taking the role of Game Designer mainly but also involved on almost all the game development processes like prototyping, work planning, task creation and assignment, programming, design, testing, and deployment to stores.

As a tester, I have worked on planning and executing test plans, communicating with clients and teammates to make sure the expected requirements are clear and tested on time.

# **Employment History**

### Principal Game Designer at Timba Games, Remote

MARCH 2022 — NOVEMBER 2022

- Game Design Document and Game Flow Authoring.
- · PvP Combat Design and Balance.
- · Character Statistics Design.
- UX design for all game main screens.
- · Testing and Follow up of customer issues.
- · NPC characters Dialog Authoring.

### Staff Advanced QA at Oktana Corporation, Remote

SEPTEMBER 2020 — MARCH 2022

- Daily meetings, Sprint Planning meetings, Retrospective meetings.
- · Regression testing before and after product releases.
- Write and execute manual tests for Salesforce products.
- Testing and Follow up of customer issues.
- Manage team members to execute test cases.

### Junior Automation QA at Jalasoft, Cochabamba - Bolivia

SEPTEMBER 2018 — AUGUST 2020

- Ownership of features on QA side.
- Planning, writing and executing tests to cover feature requirements.
- Issue track and Testing Planning using Jira.
- Manual and Automation web/rest testing using Selenium, Javascript, Python, Postman, Excel.

## Unity 3D Programmer/2D animator at Xiara Studios, Remote

 ${\tt MARCH~2016-JANUARY~2018}$ 

- Sprint Planning and Daily meetings within a team up to 10 members using Trello
- Github merge, rebase, create and review pull requests.
- Programming Gameplay and Multiplayer Features for 2D Fighting game for Android Platforms.
- · 2D assets integration with code.
- 2D animations for playable characters.

# **Education**

**Quality Automation Training Program, Fundacion JALA, Cochabamba** 

JANUARY 2018 — SEPTEMBER 2018

High School Diploma, Puerto de Mejillones, Cochabamba

JANUARY 2008 — DECEMBER 2012